November Criminals is a crime, drama, mystery film directed by Sacha Gervasi.
When Addison investigates the murder of his friend Kevin with the help of Phoebe,
they discover that the truth is darker than they had ever imagined.
Addison, played by Ansel Elgort.
Phoebe, played by Chloë Grace Moretz.
Theo, played by David Strathairn.
Fiona, played by Catherine Keener.
Principal Karlstadt, played by Terry Kinney.
D. Cash, played by Cory Hardrict.
November Criminals is a 2017 American crime drama film, directed by Sacha Gervasi and written by
Gervasi and Steven Knight, and based on Sam Munson's 2010 novel The November Criminals.
The film stars Ansel Elgort, Chloë Grace Moretz,
Catherine Keener, and David Strathairn.
The film was released through video on demand on November 7, 2017, and opened in a limited
release on December 8, 2017, by Stage 6 Films and Vertical Entertainment.
The film explores themes of high school, based on novel
or book, murder, drugs, death of mother.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.